I'm Sakura Minamoto, and today, my second year of high school begins!
I can be kind of a klutz most of the time, and there are days when it feels like I really don't have it together.
But luckily, it's not gonna be like that anymore.
I'm gonna be the girl I always wanted to be.
If I follow my dreams, I know my future will be full of happiness and excitement.
Here I go!
Oh!
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
I... I...
Okay, I think I'm far enough away.
Sokka?
Is that where I am?
Hey, little girl!
You're not supposed to be out this late!
What are you trying to do?
Get arrested?
Cause I'll do it!
All I'm trying to do is clock out and go home.
I'm soaking wet down to my underpants here!
Officer, please! I need help!
What the...
Are you...
Stay back!
What's wrong with you?
Huh? I...
Huh?
Ah!
Now where am I?
What happened to me? Why do I look so... It's all a blank. I can't remember. What am I?
You're Sakura Minamoto.
It's... you again.
You were killed by a truck ten years ago.
Uh, I was what?
But now you've returned to life as a zombie.
I'm a... zombie?
Your vital mission is to assume this new identity as Zombie One and work with the rest of your team to save the Saga Prefecture.
Look, sir, I'm sorry, but I don't know what you're talking about.
You'll understand soon enough.
Listen, as long as you follow my instructions exactly, I promise you'll probably be fine.
Um, why?
My name is Kotaro Tatsumi.
It's totally weird that he's got...
I'm the man who's going to turn you into a pop idol!
Why does he... have squid in his pocket?
혼자, he's fucking mad.
Ha!
Hello, and good morning, ladies!
I said good morning!
Sorry! Good morning!
You should mind your manners.
That's the only way to make sure that people respect you.
I mean, look! Everyone's ignoring you!
Morning, Romero!
Good job wrangling the girls, as always!
Let's begin!
Time to work extra hard to make you world-class idols!
Um, real quick...
Yes, you! And by the way, your complexion's looking radiant today!
I just have... a question.
By all means, bring it on!
I'm dead. Like, actually dead. Right?
Dead as dirt. And now your zombie won.
And just how did that happen to me, sir?
Come on. Didn't you ever see a horror movie when you had a heartbeat?
Uh... well, yeah. Of course.
Then there's your answer.
Um, is that all?
Why does there have to be more?!
A little of this, a little of that, and bang! You're out of the grave!
That's all you need to make a zombie, kiddo!
So, got any more questions?
Uh... several, actually.
Like, why is it so important for me to be an idol?
Because you're going to save Saga.
Just by singing and dancing?
Yes, that's right.
The concept of local celebrities is becoming a thing of the past.
But that also means most of the competitions died out.
Our strategy is to capitalize on that to revitalize Saga,
which is hurtling toward irrelevance in much the same way.
And boom!
Welcome to the Zombieland Saga Project, baby!
That's nice and all, but I don't remember anything from when I was alive.
So, asking me to become a pop star and save the whole prefecture is kind of a big deal.
Not to worry. The others have much more baggage than you do.
Uh... so, who are these girls?
Curious.
Well, yeah. Sorta.
I mean, when someone's bitten you 13 times in one day, you start to wonder stuff like that.
They are legends.
Like, famous?
Correct.
Each girl is a unique and shining star I've hand-selected for the mission of saving the Saga Prefecture.
And with you, we've finally assembled the perfect group.
She conquered all of Kyushu at the turn of the century as the leader of the Dorami Biker Gang!
Cower before the legendary Saki Nikaido!
This girl single-handedly gave rise to the idol boom of the 1980s!
The legendary Showa period idol, Junko Kono!
From the turbulent times spanning the death of the Shogunate into the Meiji era,
the legendary courtesan known only as Yugiri!
After her debut in a long-running period drama, she left her mark on every network in the nation!
Legendary child actress prodigy, Lily Hoshikawa!
After the year 2000, when all the major idol groups were at war,
she was the implacable center for the number one group, Iron Frill!
Legendary Hisei period idol, I miss it all!
Wait, isn't she...?
The legendary Tai-O-Meter!
Huh?
And now you know everything you need to know about the rest of the girls!
Wait, hang on a second!
Hm?
Who's she?
The legendary Tai-O-Meter!
Uh...
Sorry, I think I missed something. Could you repeat that?
The legendary...
Tai-O-Meter!
Okay...
I know what her name is, but...
Is there more?
Does there need to be more?!
But what's her legend?!
Who says a legend has to be anything?!
Oh yeah, that's right!
Nobody!
So she's just a regular zombie?!
Well, what makes you so legendary, huh, Sakura?!
Not a damn thing!
From now on, I'll say they're all legendary except you!
Anyway, at this point, they're all your stereotypical run-of-the-mill zombies.
They haven't yet awakened.
That's a thing?
Yes.
But I figure with a little stimulation like you had, they'll eventually regain their consciousness.
Huh?
Stimulation?!
What happened to me anyway?!
Speaking of which, you girls are going to put on a stimulating live performance!
Hey, don't just ignore me!
Uh...
Wait, what?
Your first show is...
Tonight!
What is this?
Huh?
What's up, Dr Soda?
What is this?
This is a death metal concert.
It's the only place with an open stage policy.
We shouldn't be here. We're gonna bomb!
Hey, you! What are you doing?
Don't chew on that! This equipment is expensive!
Thanks to the awesome makeup techniques I learned in Hollywood,
it'll be impossible to figure out that you're zombies.
That doesn't solve anything!
It is good, though.
You say that now, but yesterday you went and passed out as soon as I tried it on you.
Guess that's the thanks I get for making you a star.
Uh, Tai?
Okay, this is weird even for her! What the heck is going on?!
This is bad! How are we gonna explain this?!
You've got this.
I think it should be obvious by now that I don't!
Chill out. What's the big deal?
Chill out? How am I supposed to chill out, huh?!
I'm the only one who isn't lipping around the room trying to eat everything!
And besides that, aren't you supposed to rehearse before you get on stage?!
What do you expect us to perform?!
All I need you to do is trust in your instincts.
Well, my instincts say Tai's gonna bite people.
A zombie bite never hurt anybody!
Not too bright, are you?
Okay!
The good news is this crowd doesn't know you,
so the expectations are so small they're basically non-existent!
Same goes for me. I fully expect you'll blow it!
Then why?
Let me finish!
That's why you have to surprise us!
You can turn Saga, no, the entire world upside down,
if you give it everything you've got!
Really? You think so?
Hey, Death Musume, title not final, you're up next!
Have faith. You'll do fine.
Oh, Kotaro, I... can't do it.
Okay then! It's go time!
Now get out there and knock them dead, ladies!
Um, good evening ladies and gentlemen at the Medal of Persuasion.
We're a brand new idol group called Death Musume,
so we hope you, uh, like us...
Spit it out or get off the stage, sister!
Why the hell is there an idol group here?
Yeah, you better not be making fun of Death Metal!
I'm not, I swear! Here goes.
And by the way, you can all call me number one.
Who cares?! Just start playing already!
I'm sure it's just a pile of mainstream pop rubbish!
I'm sorry I really am!
They're so mad! What do I do now?
I knew this would happen!
A stage dive?
But they haven't even studied it!
I feel bad for grabbing her like this,
but I think she might eat my face!
Cut that out! Let him go!
I've never seen anyone stocked their set with a moss pit.
Whoa, that chick is actually kind of brutal.
It's a disaster!
We'll never come back from this!
Now what?
Music! Come on!
We're singing to this?!
Oh, no way!
I thought it was gonna be some idle crap!
Maybe they're playing the wrong track!
I like it!
Show us what you got, girlies!
Yeah!
We'll see the end!
Noooooo!
What do I do?!
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
How is this possible, man? No one should be able to have a thing like that! It's like their necks are freakin' broken!
Oh, this feels kind of... annoying.
Yeah! Yeah!
I don't think we changed the world.
But still, I wonder what that feeling was.
Tai!
Help!
What's happening here?
Please, somebody do something!
I'm so scared!
Oh, dear.
What a terrible racket.
Slept like the dead.
What to say?
Let's see here.
Good morning, everybody!
Party!
Joe!
Sakura here! Well, there you go! We're zombies! Not only that, we're gonna be idols, too!
Now that everyone's awake, I hope we all get along!
Next time, episode 2, I Love Hip Hop Saga! Please check it out!